boylesports.com 2015-04-19

# 

At Boylesports we care about your privacy and we respect your privacy rights.

By using the Boylecasino, Boylepoker, Boylegames or Boylebingo Website you permit the collection and use of your personal information as outlined below and you signify your agreement to this Privacy Policy last updated on 16th August 2010. If you do not agree with these terms, you should not use any of the Websites and/or the Boylecasino, Boylepoker, Boylegames or Boylebingo Services. 

The following discloses information gathering and dissemination practices for the website.

1\. About our Privacy Policy

1.1 Boylesports is registered with the Guernsey Data Protection Agency, registration number: 011643. 

1.2 Our websites http://www.boylesports.com/casino/, http://www.boylesports.com/poker, http://www.boylesports.com/games and http://www.boylesports.com/bingo all pages containing these addresses (each website and related pages being a "Website") and the services provided on each Website (the "Boylecasino Services" "Boylepoker Services" "Boylegames Services" and "Boylebingo Services") are operated by Boylesports Alderney Limited, company registration number 1627, having its registered office at, C/o The Fort Group, York House, Victoria Street, Alderney, GY9 3TA ("we", "us" "Boylesports" and "our").

The Website Terms describe the Boylecasino Services, the Boylepoker Services, the Boylegames Services and the Boylebingo Services provided to the public via the Websites. 

1.3 This policy (together with our Terms and any other documents referred to on it) sets out the basis on which any personal data we collect from you, or that you provide to us, will be processed by us. Please read the following carefully to understand our views and practices regarding your personal data and how we will treat it. 

2\. How we collect information on the website

2.1 When registering as a user of a Website or during your time as a user of a Website you will be asked to provide information to us. We will inform you at the time of collecting information from you whether you must provide the information to use a Website or a particular Boylecasino Service, a Boylepoker Service, Boylegames Service and/or a Boylebingo Service, or whether the provision of information requested by us is optional

2.2 You agree that your username and name may be shown to other users of Websites and the Boylecasino Services if you win the MegaJackpots Game or other Poker Games, Casino Games or Bingo Games played on a Website. In all other cases we will endeavour to inform you at the time of collecting the information from you whether the information that you provide to us will be accessible to other users of the Website or by third parties so that you can decide whether to provide the information to us.

2.3 We may collect and process the following data about you:

2.3.1 your title, gender, forename, surname, date of birth, nationality, email, address, phone number, account currency, affiliate reference, username, encrypted password, payment details

2.3.2 an internationally recognised photo ID (passport, driving licence), a utility bill, proof of identity, residence and/or age, and/or a bank or credit card statement relating to your payment details that are registered with us; 

2.3.3 if you contact us, we may keep a record of that correspondence; 

2.3.4 information that you submit in response to a surveys or poll; 

2.3.5 details of transactions you carry out through a Website and your account number with us; and

2.3.6 details of your visits to a Website including, but not limited to, game play records, traffic data, location data, weblogs and other communication data, whether this is required for our own billing purposes or otherwise and the resources that you access.

3\. Uses made of the information

3.1 We collect and use information from users of the Website for the following purposes:

3.1.1 setting up, operating and managing your Account;

3.1.2 providing the Boylecasino Service, the Boylepoker Service, the Boylegames Service and/or the Boylebingo Service requested by you from us using a Website and to carry out our obligations arising from any contracts entered into between you and us; 

3.1.3 reviewing and determining your eligibility to use a Website or open an account with us;

3.1.4 to enable us to carry out statistical and other analysis; 

3.1.5 verifying the accuracy of your Information, including disclosure of such information to third parties (including financial institutions, software providers (e.g. WagerWorks), identity verification, age verification and credit reporting agencies) in connection with such purposes (a record of the search will be retained and the third party may use the information to assist other companies for verification purposes); 

3.1.6 verifying the payment details that you have provided to us, including the address of your card;

3.1.7 confirming the details that you have provided to us in relation to your account; 

3.1.8 verifying your eligibility to win or place a Bet on the Website;

3.1.9 contacting you using your contact details to tell you about changes to a Website, the Boylecasino Services, the Boylepoker Services, the Boylegames Service and/or the Boylebingo Services, technical or security issues, updates and changes to this Policy or our Terms; 

3.1.10 complying with our regulatory and legal obligations;

3.1.11 providing customer support services;

3.1.12 ensuring that content from a Website is presented in an effective manner for you and for your computer; 

3.1.13 providing you with information regarding our products or services that you request from us or which we feel may interest you, where you have consented to be contacted for such purposes; or 

3.1.14 allowing you to participate in interactive features of our service or Website, when you choose to do so.

3.2 Except as set out in this Privacy Policy, we do not sell, rent, share, trade or give away any of your personal information to third parties. We do give your personal information to third parties who/which operate Poker Games or Casino Games on a Website for us for the purposes of providing you with the Boylecasino Services, the Boylepoker Services, the Boylegames Services and/or the Boylebingo Services, to payment processers for purposes relating to the Boylecasino Services, the Boylepoker Services, the Boylegames Services and/or the Boylebingo Services, to third party affiliates who/which direct users to a Website for the purposes of confirming commission or other related purposes and to other third parties for the purposes of verifying information that you provided to us (e.g. provision of information to banks for verifying credit card payments). 

3.3 We may also use your email address or your postal address to send you updates or news regarding a Website, the Boylecasino Services, the Boylepoker Services, the Boylegames Services and/or the Boylebingo Services, but you may choose not to receive emails of this type by accessing the "My Account" tab of the Boylesports Website (www.boylesports.com) and updating your "My Preferences" settings. 

4\. Disclosure of your information to other people

4.1 We will not disclose to any third party personal information that you provide to us unless (i) we have your permission, (ii) it is required or permitted by law, or (iii) your agreement with us permits such disclosure. 

4.2 If you provide personal information to us, you understand and agree that we may disclose your personal information for the following purposes to the following third parties: 

4.2.1 if you have indicated at registration, or at any time during your time as a user of the Website, that you are happy to receive information or promotions from selected third parties about goods and services which may be of interest to you, you consent to us sending your information to such third parties so that they may provide you with such offers or information. You may opt out of receiving such offers or change your preferences at any time by emailing [care@boylesports.com](mailto:care@boylesports.com)

4.2.2 to any member of our group of companies, which means our subsidiaries, our ultimate holding company and its subsidiaries; 

4.2.3 to the prospective seller or buyer of any business or assets related to a Website or all or part of Boylesports Alderney Limited in respect of the sale;

4.2.4 to a third party if we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal data with that third party in order to comply with any legal obligation, or in order to enforce or apply our Terms and other agreements, or to protect the rights, property, or safety of Boylesports Alderney Limited, our customers, or others. This includes exchanging information with third parties for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction; 

4.2.5 any operator, payment processor, verification service provide, marketing partners that/who provide services to us in relation to the Websites, including any person specifically named in our Terms or in other agreements that form part of our agreement with you; and/or

4.2.6 to our licensors, the Alderney Gambling Control Commission (AGCC) and the Gambling Commission of Great Britain, which requires unrestricted access to all player details and records in order to regulate the online gambling industry and to ensure that it is conducted honestly and fairly and remains free from criminal influence, or any other licensing or regulatory authority which we may deal with in relation to a Website.

4.3 We will notify you when information about you may be provided to third parties in ways other than explained above and you will have the option to prevent such information sharing at the time that we notify you. 

4.4 We do not disclose personal information about you to third parties (including advertisers or marketing companies), but we may provide them with aggregate anonymised information about Website users. For example, we may inform them that 500 men aged under 30 have clicked on their advertisement or have played a particular game on a Website on any given day, or we might inform third parties regarding the number of unique users who visit Website, the demographic breakdown of our community users of Website or the activities that visitors to Website engage in while on Website. We may also use such aggregate anonymised information to help advertisers reach the kind of audience they want to target. We may make use of the personal data we have collected from you to enable us to comply with our advertisers wishes by displaying their advertisement to that target audience. 

4.5 In connection with the provision of our services, we may need to transfer data, including personal information, to other companies not incorporated in the same jurisdiction. You agree that we may transfer personal information we hold about you to any country, including countries outside the European Economic Area, in accordance with this Privacy Policy. 

4.6 As a user of either Website you agree that: 

4.6.1Boylesports Isle of Man Limited will be processing your registration form on behalf of Boylesports Alderney Limited on its servers in the Isle of Man; and

4.6.2 the information that you give Boylesports Isle of Man Limited (acting as agent of Boylesports Alderney Limited) when registering (including, but not limited to, title, gender, forename, surname, date of birth, email, address, phone number, account currency, affiliate reference, username, encrypted password) is passed from Boylesports Isle of Man Limited to Boylesports Alderney Limited.

4.7 You acknowledge and agree that the Boylepoker Website including all casino-style games available on that website, is hosted in Alderney. The gaming servers are located in Kahnawake. The Boylecasino Website, and any casino-style games available on the Boylepoker Website, are hosted and administered by us out of Alderney and are licensed and regulated from the regulated jurisdiction of Alderney. 

5\. Security and control of your personal data

5.1 We will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy. 

5.2 Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password which enables you to access certain parts of a Website, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share your password with anyone. 

5.3 Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the Internet is not completely secure. Although we will do our best to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to a Website; any transmission is at your own risk. Once we have received your information, we will use strict procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorised access. You acknowledge that we are not responsible for any intercepted information sent via the Internet, and you hereby release us from any and all claims arising out of or related to the use of intercepted information in any unauthorised manner. 

5.4 As a registered user of either/all Website(s), the Boylecasino Services, the Boylepoker Services, the Boylegames Service and/or the Boylebingo Services you can modify your personal information at any time by accessing the "My Account" section of the Boylesports Website or by contacting us at care@boylesports.com. 

6\. Links to third party websites

6.1 Either Website may, from time to time, contain links to and from the websites of our partner networks, advertisers and affiliates as well as third party websites to which we have no affiliation. If you follow a link to any of these websites, please note that these websites have their own privacy policies and that we do not accept any responsibility or liability for these policies. 

7\. Telephone Services

Telephone calls to and from our any of our telephone numbers may be recorded for training and/or security purposes. 

8\. IP addresses and cookies

8.1 We may collect information about your computer, including (where available) your IP address, operating system and browser type, for system administration, statistical purposes. This is statistical data about our users browsing actions and patterns, and does not identify any individual. 

8.2 For the same reason, we may obtain information about your general internet usage by using a cookie file which is stored on the hard drive of your computer. Cookies contain information that is transferred to your computer hard drive. On revisiting the Websites our computer server will recognise the cookie, giving us information about your last visit. They help us to improve the Websites and to deliver a better and more personalised service. They enable us: 

8.2.1 to estimate our user size and usage pattern;

8.2.2 to store information about your preferences, and so allow us to customise the Websites according to your individual interests; and

8.2.3 to speed up your searches. 

8.3 You may refuse to accept cookies by activating the setting on your browser which allows you to refuse the setting of cookies. However, if you select this setting you may be unable to access certain parts of the Websites. Unless you have adjusted your browser setting so that it will refuse cookies, our system will issue cookies when you log on to a Website.

8.4 For information on how to control your cookies go to [www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/).

9\. Access to information and updating, verifying and deleting personal data

9.1 At any time, you can make a written request to have access to all the personal information that we hold about you. We will provide this information to you and may request a small administrative charge.

9.2 You may inform us of any changes in your personal data and in accordance with our obligations to you; we will update or delete your personal data accordingly. 

10\. Changes to our privacy policy

Any changes we may make to our Privacy Policy in the future will be posted on this page and, where appropriate, notified to you by email. You should visit this page periodically to review any changes to the Privacy Policy. 

11\. User feedback and complaints

Questions, comments and requests regarding this Privacy Policy are welcomed and should be addressed to care@boylesports.com.
